Damn
Oh my god
Three-legged forest frogs
Pouncing on people like crazy
Scared me to death
Oh my god
All forest frogs in the greenhouse mutated and died
Is Daniel cursed
How could this happen
These frogs of yours ate
Excessive doses of hormone feed
Causing genetic mutations
Daniel
How dare you sell me
The hormone-fed forest frogs
I didn't feed them hormones
My feed formula
Is exactly the same as Lewes's
His are perfectly fine
How could mine have problems
It's mixed with
Special feed from Health Biotech
Which contains lots of hormones
That salesman came to my place too
I rejected him on the spot
Because I know
This kind of feed
Even though it can make frogs
Gain weight quickly in a short time
But at the cost of their lifespan
Deformity and sudden death
Are just a matter of time
Jason
Didn't you say you used
Lewes's formula
What is going on
Boss
I
I was forced to do it
You said if I didn't figure out the formula in five days
You would kick me out
I had no choice
So I had to buy that special feed to fake it